Guide to the Richard Maass Collection of Westchester and New York State 1645-1995, (Bulk: 1645-1910) MSS.055
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Printed Materials
  - Subseries A: Newspapers and Other Printed Materials
    - Fighting for Freedom "Four Years of English Rule in Ireland" place: New Rochelle, Apr 17; 1 pages (Box 14, Folder 62)
      physical description: full sheet, handbill
      dimensions: 18cm x 26.5cm
      Advertisement for a Lecture by Mr. J.M. Wall.
  - Subseries B: Richard Maass' Transcriptions and Notes
    This subseries, held in boxes 17 through 19, holds transcriptions and notes made by Richard Maass regarding the materials contained in and separated from Series V subseries A. No container list has been made for this subseries.
    Box 17 contains materials regarding The Boston Chronicle, The Boston Gazette and Country Journal, The Caledonian Mercury, The Columbian Centinel, The Connecticut Courant, The Connecticut Journal, The Connecticut Observer, The Continental Journal, Drewby's Derby Mercury, Dunlap's Pennsylvania Packet, The Edinburgh Advertiser, Essex Gazette, Essex Journal, Essex Register, The Exeter Watchman, The Freeman's Journal, The Gazetteer, Gentleman's Magazine, and Gazette de France (January 1776 - February 1783). One folder, labeled "The Boston Chronicle Dec. 26 1768 and Other Xeroxes," also contains transcriptions and photocopies of correspondence located in Series I.
    Box 18 contains materials regarding Gazette de France (March 1783 - December 1783), The Glasgow Mercury, The Independent Chronicle, The Independent Ledger, Lloyd's Evening Post, London Chronicle, London Gazette, Maryland Journal, The Morning Post and Daily Advertiser, The National Intelligencer and Washington Advertiser, New England Chronicle, New England Galaxy, The New England Palladium, New Jersey Gazette, New York Packet, Niles' Weekly Register, Pennsylvania Evening Post, Pennsylvania Gazette, Pennsylvania Journal Supplement, The Pennsylvania Ledger, The Pennsylvania Packet, Providence Gazette, St. James Chronicle, The Salem Gazette, Town and Country, and Ephemera (Printed Materials).
    Box 19 contains materials regarding "Nouvelles Extraordinaires de Divers Endroits."
- Series VI: Accretions
  - Subseries A: Charles Lee
    Subseries A contains letters to and from General Charles Lee.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: s.l., undated; 055-006-A-2069; 6 pages (Box 20, Folder 1)
      physical description: six half sheets, edge damage and repairs; a.m.
      Notes about English history, particularly Charles I. Published as "A Political Essay" in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1874." (Vol. IV of the Lee Papers, pp. 100-108).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: [Ireland], Aug 4, [1754]; 055-006-A-2076; 3 pages (Box 20, Folder 2)
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee)
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: [Ireland], Jan 2, [1754]; 055-006-A-2080; 3 pages (Box 20, Folder 3)
      dimensions: 37cm x 22cm
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Recounts voyage from England to Ireland.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Schenectada (i.e. Schenectady, NY), Jun 18, [1756?]; 055-006-A-2084; 6 pages (Box 20, Folder 4)
      physical description: three half sheets; a.l.s.
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Description of natives and fighting conditions of French and Indian War. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 2-6).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Niagara, Jul 30, [1759]; 055-006-A-2091; 3 pages (Box 20, Folder 5)
      physical description: full sheet, trimmed; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 46cm x 26cm
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Report of the fall of Niagara. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 19-20).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Philadelphia, Mar 1, [1760]; 055-006-A-2095; 5 pages (Box 20, Folder 6)
      physical description: full sheet folded, plus single half sheet; a.l.s.
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Scouting expedition from Niagara to Fort Duquesne. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 26-30).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: London, [Nov 29, 1760]; 055-006-A-2101; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 7)
      dimensions: 39cm x 23cm
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Anticipates introduction to Pitt.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: [London?], Feb 10, [1761]; 055-006-A-2102; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 8)
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 31).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: London, Feb 19, [1761]; 055-006-A-2103; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 9)
      physical description: half sheet with wax fragments, crease is almost entirely split; a.l.s.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: London, Jul 4, [1761]; 055-006-A-2302; 3 pages (Box 20, Folder 9.5)
      dimensions: 38cm x 22cm
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Lisbon, Jul 21, 1762; 055-006-A-2106; 4 pages (Box 20, Folder 10)
      physical description: full sheet folded, torn along crease; a.l.s.
      To "My Dr Lord" Report on Portugese troops.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Abrantes, Portugal, Aug 24, 1762; 055-006-A-2111; 6 pages (Box 20, Folder 11)
      physical description: full sheet folded, additional half sheet attached; a.l.s.
      To "My Dr Lord" (William Petty, Earl of Shelburne) Report on Portugese situation.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Warsaw, Apr 3, 1764; 055-006-A-2118; 7 pages (Box 20, Folder 12)
      To "My Dr Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Account of visit to Berlin and Warsaw.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: London, Nov 17, 1764; 055-006-A-2126; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 13)
      To "My Lord" Requests letter of reference to secure a position as a mercenary in Poland
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Constantinople, Mar 1, 1766; 055-006-A-2129; 3 pages (Box 20, Folder 14)
      dimensions: 45cm x 25cm
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Travels from Moscow to Constantinople.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Constantinople, May 28, 1766; 055-006-A-2133; 3 pages (Box 20, Folder 15)
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Responds to news of their mother's death. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 44-45).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: London, Feb 6, 1767; 055-006-A-2137; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 16)
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Waiting to hear about promotion.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Barton, Apr 21, 1768; 055-006-A-2140; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: London, Nov 29, 1768; 055-006-A-2143; 4 pages (Box 20, Folder 18)
      physical description: half sheet folded, backed with silk; a.l.s.
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Outlines plans to join the Russian army to fight the Turks. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 67-69).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: London, Dec 21, 1768; 055-006-A-2148; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 19)
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) On leaving England for Corsica via France.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Vienna, Feb 12, 1769; 055-006-A-2151; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 20)
      physical description: half sheet folded, wax fragments; a.l.s.
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) In Vienna en route to Warsaw.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Muncaes, Hungary, Sep 30, [1769]; 055-006-A-2152; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 21)
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Complains about campaign and health. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 86-87).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Leghorn, Mar 27, 1771; 055-006-A-2155; 3 pages (Box 20, Folder 22)
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Travel plans.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Lyons, Mar 28, [1772]; 055-006-A-2159; 6 pages (Box 20, Folder 23)
      physical description: half sheet folded, additional fragment; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 31cm x 20cm
      To "Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Travels in France and personal observations.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Philadelphia, May 13, [1775]; 055-006-A-2166; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 24)
      To "My Dr Gates" (General Gates) Purchase of estate in Berkeley County, VA. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, p. 179)
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: en route to Philadelphia, [Jun 13/14, 1775]; 055-006-A-2167; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 25)
      To "Sir" (John Page) Thanks Page for his hospitality.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Camp at Winter Hill, Aug 2, 1775; 055-006-A-2168; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 26)
      To "Dr Schyler" (Major General Schuyler) Opinions on current fortifications and campain against Canada
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: s.l., Aug 14, [1775]; 055-006-A-2169; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 27)
      dimensions: 14cm x 19cm
      To "Dr Sir" (Mr. Commissary Trumbul) Requests joists and boards for his house.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Prospect Hill, Aug 23, [1775]; 055-006-A-2170; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 28)
      To "Sir" (General George Washington) Regarding an accused Tory in Newport
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Berkely County, VA, Oct 2, 1775; 055-006-A-2171; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 29)
      physical description: half sheet, torn edges; a.d.s.
      Contract for purchase of land from Jacob Hite.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Camp before Boston, Oct 24, [1775]; 055-006-A-2174; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 30)
      dimensions: 21cm x 22cm
      Letter of reference for Walton White, Esq.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Cambridge, MA, Dec 12, 1775; 055-006-A-2175; 4 pages (Box 20, Folder 31)
      To "Dr Rush" (Benjamin Rush) Comments on British commanders. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 226-228).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: New Haven, CT, Jan 16, 1776; 055-006-A-2180; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 32)
      physical description: badly damaged fragment; a.l.s.
      To (Col. Waterburg) Fragment of letter without Notes.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Stamford, CT, Jan 28, 1776; 055-006-A-2183; 3 pages (Box 20, Folder 33)
      physical description: two half sheets; a.l.s.
      To "Sir" (Alex McDougall) Lee pleads with McDougall to fully commit to the rebel cause.
    - creator: Alexander, William [Lord Stirling] place: Elizabeth Town, NJ, Feb 4, 1776; 055-006-A-2187; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 34)
      dimensions: 16cm x 20cm
      To "My Dear General" (Charles Lee) Reply to Lee's request for troops
    - creator: McDougall, Alexander place: New York, NY, Feb 7, 1776; 055-006-A-2188; 4 pages (Box 20, Folder 35)
      To "Dear Sir" (Charles Lee) Report on the defence of New York City.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: New York, NY, Feb 21, 1776; 055-006-A-2193; 4 pages (Box 20, Folder 36)
      physical description: half sheet folded, with additional envelope fragment; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 44cm x 27cm
      To "Dr Morris" (Robert Morris) Long political letter on recent developments. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1871." (Vol. I of the Lee Papers, pp. 317-320).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: New York, NY, Feb 26, 1776; 055-006-A-2198; 4 pages (Box 20, Folder 37)
      To "My Dr Rush" (Benjamin Rush) Suggests King George should be beheaded.
    - creator: Steuben, Baron place: s.l., undated, [1776]; 055-006-A-2203; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 38)
      physical description: fragment; a.l.
      Steuben's opinion on Congress's decision to indemnify Lee for his losses.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: New York, NY, Feb 29, 1776; 055-006-A-2204; 1 pages (Box 20, Folder 39)
      dimensions: 18cm x 10cm
      To "Sir" ("Commissary of Stores - or the Barrack Master") Requests beds and kettles for Colonel Ward's men.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Charleston, SC, Jul 2, 1776; 055-006-A-2205; 3 pages (Box 12, Folder 8)
      physical description: half sheet, cut in half; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 25cm x 31cm
      To "Dr Morris" (Robert Morris) Requests money after victory in S.C. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1872." (Vol. II of the Lee Papers, pp 117-119).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Charleston, SC, Jul 3, 1776; 055-006-A-2209; 1 pages (Box 12, Folder 9)
      physical description: fragment, multiple repairs; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 23cm x 25cm
      To "Sir" (President of the Provincial Council of North Carolina) Report of victory. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1872." (Vol. II of the Lee Papers, p. 120).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Camp [White Plains, NY], Nov 20, 1776; 055-006-A-2210; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 42)
      To "My Dr Rush" (Benjamin Rush) Critical remarks about fall of Fort Washington. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1872." (Vol. II of the Lee Papers, pp. 288-289).
    - creator: Lee, Charles, Nov 20, 1776 - Nov 26, 1776; 055-006-A-2213; 16 pages (Box 20, Folder 43)
      physical description: two sheets in quarto, disbound; MS
      Lee's letter book from November 1776, including copies of three letters to George Washington.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Panton, NJ, Dec 7, 1776; 055-006-A-2230; 2 pages (Box 20, Folder 44)
      To "Dear Sir" (Governor Nicholas Cooke) Presents Marquis de Malmedy to Rhode Island governor. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1872." (Vol. II of the Lee Papers, pp. 331-332).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Panton, NJ, Feb 9, 1777; 055-006-A-2233; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 45)
      Address leaf of letter from Lee to Robert Morris or Benjamin Rush. No letter of this date to Morriis or Rush in Lee Papers at N-YHS.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: New York, NY, Apr 4, 1777; 055-006-A-2234; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 46)
      To "Giuseppi" (Giuseppi Minghieri) Presents Marquis de Malmedy to Rhode Island governor. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1872." (Vol. II of the Lee Papers, pp. 367-368).
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: New York, NY, Dec 15, 1777; 055-006-A-2235; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 47)
      physical description: full sheet folded, fragments missing; a.l.s.
      To "My Dr Sister" (Miss Sidney Lee) Written from captivity in New York. Published in "Collections of the New-York Historical Society for the Year 1872." (Vol. II of the Lee Papers, pp. 375).
    - creator: Anonymous place: Panton, NJ, [1777]; 055-006-A-2236; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 48)
      physical description: fragment; MS
      Notes in a contemporary hand, re: Lee, probably shortly after his capture by the British.
    - creator: Lee, Sidney place: Oswestry, England, Mar 13, 1778; 055-006-A-2239; 3 pages (Box 21, Folder 49)
      To "Dear Brother" (Charles Lee) Family news.
    - creator: Lott, Abraham place: Bererwyck, Apr 20, 1778; 055-006-A-2243; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 50)
      To "Dear General" (Charles Lee) Congratulates Lee on his release from the British.
    - creator: Lee, Sidney place: Oswestry, England, Jun 21, 1778; 055-006-A-2244; 4 pages (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - creator: Crocker, Joseph place: White Plains, NY, Jul 10, 1778; 055-006-A-2249; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 52)
      To "Sir" (Samuel Mather) Description of Lee's disobedience at Monmouth.
    - creator: Selden, Ezra place: White Plains, NY, Aug 11, 1778; 055-006-A-2252; 3 pages (Box 21, Folder 53)
      To "Sir" (Dr. Samuel Mather) Congratulates Lee on his release by the British.
    - creator: (1778) Lee, Charles place: Saw Pitts, Aug 13, [1778]; 055-006-A-2256; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 54)
      physical description: two half sheets, address leaf damaged with wax fragments; a.l.s.
      To "Dr Rush" (Benjamin Rush) Regarding court 1artial.
    - creator: Edwards, Everett place: Philadelphia, PA, Aug 30, 1778; 055-006-A-2259; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 55)
      To "My dear Genrl" (Charles Lee) Expresses disbelief at verdict against Lee.
    - creator: Lee, Sidney place: Newgate Street, Jan 3, 1779; 055-006-A-2262; 3 pages (Box 21, Folder 56)
      physical description: half sheet folded; a.l.
      To "My dear Charles" (Charles Lee) Regarding his release from captivity.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Philadelphia, Jan 28, 1779; 055-006-A-2266; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 57)
      To "Madam" Highly personal letter to a woman.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Philadelphia, Apr 12, 1779; 055-006-A-2269; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 58)
      To Mr. Jonathan Garton Sight draft on London merchant.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Rio Prato, Berkeley County, Virginia, [1780]; 055-006-A-2272; 4 pages (Box 21, Folder 59)
      physical description: half sheet folded, extensive repairs; a.l.s.
      To "Dear Sir" Complaint against tenant farmer.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: s.l., undated; 055-006-A-2277; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 60)
      Notes in Lee's hand damning someone who lied about him.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Cedar Run, May 23, 1781; 055-006-A-2280; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 61)
      To Miss M. K. Goddard Business matters.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Fredericksburg, Virginia, May 29, [1780?]; 055-006-A-2283; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 62)
      To "My dr Oswald" (Colonel Oswald) Business matters concerning Mr. Goddard and Mr. Carrol.
    - creator: Lincoln, Benjamin place: s.l., Jun 8, 1782; 055-006-A-2286; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 63)
      To Charles Lee Expression of friendship and regard.
    - creator: Lee, Charles place: Berkeley County, Virginia, [1782]; 055-006-A-2289; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 64)
      physical description: half sheet, extensive repairs; a.d.
      Contemporary copy of Lee's will.
    - creator: Morris, Jacob and Everett Edwards place: Philadelphia, Jan 28, 1783; 055-006-A-2292; 3 pages (Box 21, Folder 65)
      dimensions: 42cm x 35cm
      To William Goddard Regarding Lee's will.
    - creator: Rutherford, Thomas place: Berkeley County, Virginia, Sep 4, 1787; 055-006-A-2296; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 66)
      To William Goddard. Regarding division of Lee's property.
    - creator: Sparks, Jared place: Cambridge, [MA], Oct 2, 1844; 055-006-A-2299; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 67)
      physical description: wove paper, bluish tint; a.l.s.
      To William G. Goddard. Regarding Lee MSS Sparks wants for a biography he's writing.
    - creator: Sparks, Jared place: Cambridge, [MA], Oct 17, 1844; 055-006-A-2300; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - creator: Sparks, Jared place: Cambridge, [MA], Oct 28, 1844; 055-006-A-2301; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - General Notes-Charles Lee, 1781-1995, Undated (Box 21, Folder 70)
      Includes a print-out of an article from The Political Magazine dated August 1781, a chronology describing the life of Charles Lee, a woodblock print portraying Charles Lee, a copy of The Westchester Historian Vol. 71 No. 1 dated Winter 1995, and a print-out entitled "Biography, in Brief, of Charles Lee."
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1992 (Box 21, Folder 71)
      This folder holds a copy of The New-York Historical Society Quarterly (Vol. 51 No. 1 January 1967) and a copy of Richard Maass' bookplate. It also contains clipped catalog entries regarding The Treason of General Lee by George H. Moore, the Annals of Annapolis by David Ridgely, the London Chronicle May 31-June 2 1791, the Columbian Centinel and Massachusetts Federalist, and the Memoirs of the Late Charles Lee edited by Edward Langworthy and Thomas Paine.
  - Subseries B: Letters by and about Benedict Arnold
    Subseries B contains letters by and about Benedict Arnold and is especially rich in eyewitness accounts of the events and trials surrounding his failed collaboration with the British in 1781.
    - creator: Arnold, Hannah place: s.l., Nov 10, 1753; 055-006-B-2306; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 1)
      physical description: half sheet, silked; a.l.s.
      To "Dear Child" (Benedict Arnold) Letter to Benedict at boarding school.
    - creator: Andre, John place: Quebec, Dec 1, 1774; 055-006-B-2307; 4 pages (Box 21, Folder 2)
      dimensions: 36cm x 23cm
      To Miss Louisa Andre (sister) Detailed account of his journey from New York to Quebec.
    - creator: Arnold, Benedict place: [Ticonderoga, NY], May 20, 1775; 055-006-B-2312; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 3)
      To "Dr. Sir" (Thomas Walker) Requests assistance for Capt. Nineham.
    - creator: Arnold, Benedict place: On Board the Enterprise, [May 1775]; 055-006-B-2313; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 4)
      To "Capt. Wells" Writes concerning supplies he is sending.
    - creator: Lewis, Morgan place: Albany, NY, Jul 27, 1780; 055-006-B-2314; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 5)
      To "Sir" (Colonel Udney Hay) Regarding a mare purchased from Benedict Arnold.
    - creator: Arnold, Benedict place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Aug 16, 1780; 055-006-B-2315; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 6)
      To "Dear Sir" (Timothy Pickering) Request for supplies.
    - creator: Varick, Richard place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Aug 17, 1780; 055-006-B-2318; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 7)
      physical description: full sheet, partially trimmed; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 37cm x 33cm
      To "Dear Sir" (D. Romeyn) Account of arrival at West Point and conditions there.
    - creator: Arnold, Benedict place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Sep 1, 1780; 055-006-B-2321; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 8)
      To "Madam" (Mrs. Field) Arnold seeks to purchase "milch cow" and other supplies.
    - creator: Varick, Richard place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Sep 8, 1780; 055-006-B-2322; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 9)
      To "Sir" (Ebenezer Foot) Regarding supplies of cattle.
    - creator: Arnold, Benedict, Jr. place: Needwood Academy, Maryland, Sep 11, 1780; 055-006-B-2325; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 10)
      To "Dear Papa" (Benedict Arnold)
    - creator: Arnold, Benedict place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Sep 13, 1780; 055-006-B-2326; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 11)
      Arnold authorizes payments for express riders to New Jersey.
    - creator: [Arnold, Benedict] place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Sep 6, 1780; 055-006-B-2329; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 11)
      express rider receipt
    - creator: [Arnold, Benedict] place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Sep 6, 1780; 055-006-B-2330; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - creator: [Arnold, Benedict] place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Sep 7, 1780; 055-006-B-2331; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - creator: [Arnold, Benedict] place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Sep 7, 1780; 055-006-B-2332; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 11)
      dimensions: 14cm x 10cm
    - creator: Varick, Richard place: Head Quarters Robinson's House [West Point, NY], Sep 13 and 14, 1780; 055-006-B-2333; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 12)
      To "My Dear Sir" (Reverend Derick Romeyn) Personal letter to Romeyn at Varick's father's house.
    - creator: Biddle, Clement place: Camp Tappan, Sep 26, 1780; 055-006-B-2334; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 13)
      To Colonel Timothy Pickering. Business as usual three days after Arnold's arrest.
    - creator: Strachan, William place: Tappan, Sep 26, 1780; 055-006-B-2335; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 14)
      To "Dear Sir" (Major Sabastian Bauman) Mention of discovery of Arnold's plot.
    - creator: Bedlow, William place: Clinton House, Sep 27, 1780; 055-006-B-2336; 1 pages (Box 21, Folder 15)
      To "Dear Sir" (Colonel Bauman) Requests further news of Arnold's treason.